hmart.com 2006-06-16

# Hmart.com - Quality Asian Grocery and Much More...

1\. Personal Information

If you decide to register with us, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. H Mart collects Personal Information such as, but not limited to, a person’s name and email address that are necessary for H Mart to provide you with the services offered on our site, including the prompt delivery. 

As mentioned, this Personal Information includes things like mailing address, demographic information, and preferences. All this information will be used by H Mart internally to study consumers’ patterns and trends and to create better site contents, promotions, or other miscellaneous conditions that can serve our customers more efficiently. You may elect to be included in our email list or not.

When you elect to be included in our email list and promotional or other events sponsored by H Mart, we will collect your personal information through our registration process and may also collect information about you from outside sources. All this collected information will be used to communicate and share with you about current promotion’s procedures or winning selections, our service updates, special opportunities, and future promotional events. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you can simply click on “Un-Subscription” button in our email. 

2\. How We Protect Your Personal Information

Your personal information is secured from unauthorized access from the Internet through the market leading Firewall Technology. Your information is safeguarded in the network with the best security technology and only selected staffs with authorization can view your personal information. Any personal information provided by you is also protected by the best security technology available and transmitted to H Mart’s database in secure code. 

3\. Use of Cookies 

Cookies are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer’s hardware and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. It is not necessary to use cookies to view H Mart’s website. However, you cannot save your items to the Shopping Cart unless cookies are in use for any of your On-Line Shopping experience. If you do not want to have cookies attached to your computer or your computer can not support cookies, you may have to call our call center or use alternative method suggested in our website. 

Except private information, we may exchange some information with a third party that adds cookies to your computer in order to only share statistical data.

4\. User’s Private Information Disclosure

We will not disclosure your Private Information to a third party that you voluntarily share with us during registration process or other registration process for other events. All Private Information given to us will be used by H Mart in order to study individual customer’s shopping patterns and to observe the Internet transactions occurred on the site.   
Said third party does not include website hosting partners and all other websites supporting us and our business. All these partners and websites in a business relationship with us are in an agreement that no Private Information of our customers shall be shared and disclosed.  
However, when such Private Information was shared with other companies as statistics data, it can be used by other companies for advertisement and commercial reasons. 

Additionally, H Mart can use email addresses or other Personal Information to contact you. For example, H Mart will use email addresses disclosed to deliver newsletters and special event opportunities and to notify winners of promotional events. 

In all electronically transmitted communications, you will see how you can discontinue subscription of our newsletters. If you do not desire to receive our newsletters, simply click on “un-subscription” and follow the directions. If you are registered with us, you can also find a “un-subscription” button in your Registration Information Page. 

5\. Minor 

We acknowledge that minors (individuals under 18 years of age) are using the Internet. Thus, we encourage these children to have parental or guardian permissions prior to disclosing Personal Information or to participating in our events or promotions. However, we do believe parents or guardians should play a central role in their child’s online activities and should monitor those activities to ensure that sites visited by their child are respecting their child’s privacy. We suggest to use those On-Line Services or software that controls children’s online activities by preventing children from giving out names, addresses, and other personal information without parental permissions. 

All minor users are required to provide us with the same Personal Information as ones required for Adults in order to register with us and to participate in our events or promotions. However, we reserve the right to decline registration or to ask for parental permissions depending on the age of the users.

Using cookies as mentioned previously, H Mart might collect data regarding children’s Private Information. Such collected data is used to provide the service appropriate and popular for children.

In pursuant to the law, H Mart is required to protect Personal Information of all minors. All Private Information is kept in secured network and only authorized staffs have access to this information.

All parents or guardians wishing to view their children’s Private Information in our database shall submit legal proof of their parental or guardian status to us. 

6\. Changing and Removing Personal Information and Other Information

We are committed to giving you control over your Personal Information. You can change or remove any of the Personal Information in our database. You can correct, update, or remove information and preferences you have shared with us by utilizing Private Information Menu.

7\. Links to Other Sites

Our Site provides links to other sites to provide our users with more valuable information. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible due to their own policies and rules as well as their own data collection methods. We are not responsible for those policies or activities implemented by other sites and for contents of their sites. 

All the links to other sites are suggested for your convenience and you will be responsible for everything once you enter these other sites. Nonetheless, we will make best efforts to provide you with the best quality and we value your suggestions and comments. Please tell us your comments or suggestions via our “Help” menu. 

8\. User’s Consent

Once a user visits our site, you automatically give us your consent for collection and use of your Private Information. 

We may change this policy from time to time. If we decide to change this policy in a material way, we will post notice of the change on our site via pop-up screen. You may be able to see these changes fully and comprehensively. 

9\. Suggestions

We welcome suggestions, questions, or comments on our Private Information Policy. If you have any, please suggest yours via “Help” menu on our site.
